We all have our demons.
The Cleanse is a drama, comedy, fantasy film directed by Bobby Miller.
The story of a heartbroken man who attends a spiritual retreat, only to discover that
the course releases more than everyday toxins and traumatic experiences.
Paul Berger, played by Johnny Galecki.
Maggie, played by Anna Friel.
Lily, played by Anjelica Huston.
Eric, played by Kyle Gallner.
Ken Roberts, played by Oliver Platt.
Fredericks, played by Kevin J. O'Connor.
The Cleanse is a 2016 American dark fantasy comedy film
written and directed by Bobby Miller.
The film stars Johnny Galecki, Anna Friel, Oliver Platt,
Anjelica Huston, Kyle Gallner, Kevin J.
O'Connor, and Diana Bang.
It was released on May 4, 2018, by Vertical Entertainment.
The tone is dark and lighthearted and emotional.